[
  {
    "question": "feel",
    "answer": "felt"
  },
  {
    "question": "put",
    "answer": "put"
  },
  {
    "question": "bring",
    "answer": "brought"
  },
  {
    "question": "begin",
    "answer": "began"
  },
  {
    "question": "keep",
    "answer": "kept"
  },
  {
    "question": "hold",
    "answer": "held"
  },
  {
    "question": "write",
    "answer": "wrote"
  },
  {
    "question": "stand",
    "answer": "stood"
  },
  {
    "question": "hear",
    "answer": "heard"
  },
  {
    "question": "let",
    "answer": "let"
  },
  {
    "question": "mean",
    "answer": "meant"
  },
  {
    "question": "set",
    "answer": "set"
  },
  {
    "question": "meet",
    "answer": "met"
  },
  {
    "question": "run",
    "answer": "ran"
  },
  {
    "question": "pay",
    "answer": "paid"
  }
]